<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resonating Words - Articles</title>
    <description>A beautiful narrative of poems written in hindi.</description>
    <link>
    http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog/</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>A Full and Comprehensive Style Test</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;This is just an &lt;em&gt;ipsis verbis&lt;/em&gt; copy of the first example running on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://demo.ghost.io&quot;&gt;Ghost Demo&lt;/a&gt;. This shows how you can use html styling to achieve your hopes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2014 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//a-full-and-comprehensive-style-test</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//a-full-and-comprehensive-style-test</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>KISAAN AAHAT</title>
        
          <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;i&gt;
The imagination of life without food is ridiculous. For centuries and centuries, it is the farmers who have toiled tirelessly to grow grains, fruits and vegetables to ensure our continued existence. Yet unfortunately, in India these Annadata have been so tortured by their circumstances, the government and mother nature, that for so many of them death becomes the last respite.
&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//kisaan</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//kisaan</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Melancholy</title>
        
          <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;i&gt;
Life is the home to every emotion and situation. The ups and-downs of life are what, make life worth living. If you have never seen sadness, then how can you know happniness? And if you have never known true happiness then you won&#39;t recognize sadness either.  
It is the darkness of melancholy that makes the moments of joy more bright, vibrant and colourful.
&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//gam-melancholy</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//gam-melancholy</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>ANEKROOPI</title>
        
          <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;i&gt;
A girl, a lady or a woman, or a sister, mother or wife, whatever you may choose to call her, her significance on the life of every person in this world is an undeniable fact. She looks not for sympathy, but understanding and support and works tirelessly to carve a place for herself in this world run by men.
&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//anekroopi</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://sidevesh.github.io/jasper-lit-blog//anekroopi</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
